https://www.alloysoftware.com/resources/privacy/

Privacy StatementThis statement discloses the privacy practices for alloysoftware.com websites.Information Collection and UseAlloy Software is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to other in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement.RegistrationIn order to access certain portions of this web site, a user must first complete a registration form. During registration a user is required to give their contact information. This information is used to contact the user about the services on out site for which they have expressed interest.Use of CookiesSome pages on this site use “cookies”, which are small files that the site places on your hard drive for identification purposes. These files are used for site registration and customization for the next time you visit us. Cookies cannot read data off your hard drive. Your web browser may allow you to be notified when you are receiving a cookie, giving you the choice to accept or reject it. By not accepting cookies, some pages may not fully function and you may not be able to access certain information on this site.LinksThis web site contains links to other sites operated by parties other than Alloy Software. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices on such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. The inclusion of a link does not imply any association with their operators or any endorsement of the linked site by Alloy Software.ChangesIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post the new policy on our web site under the Privacy Statement link so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. Latest NewsAlloy Software Wins Silver for Company Response of the Year During COVID-19November 23, 2020Alloy Software Wins Grand Trophy in the 10th Annual 2020 Consumer World AwardsNovember 17, 2020Service Requests Go MobileNovember 5, 2020ProductsIT Service ManagementIT Asset ManagementSoftware Asset ManagementIT Service Desk SoftwareNetwork Discovery and InventoryResourcesAwardsCompare UsNewsHIPAA ComplianceGDPR ComplianceProduct documentationSupport PortalCompanyAboutContact UsCareers
Scroll to top
